Diego Placido Acosta Torrez (+591) 77932322 Cochabamba, Bolivia

Developer - Quality Assurance

diegoacosta9239@gmail.com

PROFILE I am a technology enthusiast with experience in Front-end (React JS, Angular, Next JS) and Back-end (Express, .NET). I have skills in software quality doing automated testing, using tools such as Python, pyTest in API and Selenium, Mocha and Chai, integrated in BrowserStack and GitHub Actions for UI testing with Allure. I have 3 years of experience in IT, managing servers, equipment and routers, as well as having been an assistant in development laboratories at the Universidad Mayor de San Simón. I like to be able to meet my goals, work in a team and I have experience working under pressure.

WORK **EXPERIENCE**

Universidad Mayor de San Simon

Laboratory Assistant | 2023-2024

Support to the maintenance department, server support and network maintenance, programming instructor and software developer

ISAPCAT

Technical department | 2020-2023

Develop well-structured, computer repair and maintenance and graphic design.

Thermocontrol

Web Developer Free Lancer | 2023

Develop well-structured, maintainable code and thoroughly test your, assist the Head of IT in assessing security of web applications and action required changes arising from 3rd party pen testing of systems.

Hybrid Scripts

Web Developer | 2023

Internship where I learned new technologies, developing custom web software using Remix JS and React.

Thermocontrol

Web Implementer | **2020-2021**

Parameterization of a CRM for the implementation, server configuration for deployment and training for the use of CRM software.

Datos & Servicios

Technical Support | 2017-2020

Computer maintenance and repair, server configuration and maintenance, structured cabling, router configuration.

EDUCATION

Diploma in commercial software quality management

Universidad Mayor de San Simón | 2024, Cochabamba, Bolivia

Systems engineer

Universidad Mayor de San Simón | 2016 - 2023, Cochabamba, Bolivia

Bachelor of Humanities

Corporación Educativa Kanata | 2003 - 2015, Cochabamba, Bolivia

SKILLS

Office | JavaScript | Java | TypeScript | Python | React JS | Angular | Azure DevOps | Selenium | Pipeline GitHub Actions | BrowserStack | PyTest | Wordpress | Illustrator | Photoshop | Figma | Git | GitHub | C# | Next JS | Remix JS | express | SpringBoot | Cisco | Mikrotik | Ubiquiti | Computer maintenance and assembly | Server maintenance | .Net

IDIOMAS Spanish: Native

English: Medium